<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Perennial on The Gardening Bunny</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/perennial/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Perennial on The Gardening Bunny</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 19:22:20 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/perennial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Perennials</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/perennials/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/perennials/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Perennial plants are a fascinating category in the botanical world, known for their ability to live for more than two years, often regrowing season after season from the same roots.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hostas</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/post/hostas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 19:22:20 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/post/hostas/</guid>
      <description>Hostas Hostas are beloved for their lush foliage and ease of cultivation, making them a popular choice for gardeners seeking to add texture and vibrancy to shaded areas. These herbaceous perennials are renowned for their wide variety of leaf shapes, sizes, and colors, ranging from bold greens to striking variegations of white, cream, and gold. Hostas thrive in moist, well-drained soil and prefer partial to full shade, although some varieties can tolerate more sun with adequate moisture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Limelights</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/post/limelights/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 19:22:20 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/post/limelights/</guid>
      <description>Growing Limelight Hydrangeas Limelight hydrangeas (Hydrangea paniculata &amp;lsquo;Limelight&amp;rsquo;) are a stunning addition to any garden, renowned for their vibrant lime-green blossoms that command attention throughout the summer and into the fall.&#xA;These hardy deciduous shrubs boast large, cone-shaped flower heads that gradually transition from a creamy white in early summer to a dazzling lime-green hue as the season progresses. As autumn approaches, Limelight hydrangeas undergo yet another transformation, turning shades of pink, burgundy, and deep red, adding a spectacular finale to the garden landscape.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
